this is guy you want
to wasn't that show cancelled 28 years
ago hey Sonia do you have a guess as to
where we're going for vacation we've
been not the road for maybe 10 minutes
now so maybe how I eat how would we get
there is this public bus going under the
ocean [__] maybe it can go underwater
like a submarine or maybe it can't and
you're [__] maybe it can it can't
says who says meit yeah girl you need to
shut the [__] up hey don't you speak to
our sister like that you shut up too
[__] well anyway no one cares what you
have to say pissed assh IO boy what did
you call me
pistachio
stop mom Sonia found a new insult she
likes Sonia apologize to your clone I
will have no name callers in the royal
family but I'm a weak female there's not
much else I can
do sorry manic don't apologize for
calling me names apologize for being a
woman you loser sorry manic that's what
I like to hear [__] poopy head mama and
Al manic called me a mean name why
aren't you telling him to stop I'm a
weak female what do you expect my ass to
do about it fine I'm just going to look
out the window then and I'm going to
raise my tiny little butt so you have to
look at it the whole bus ride that will
be your punishment for not letting me
have what I want damn Sonia fine I guess
I deserve this
[__] I have had enough enough don't you
hch Hots ever get tired of talking about
big fat butts no well maybe you should
because it's really creepy what kind of
parent tells their child to put their
butt in their face that's so
disgusting Daddy please don't make me
sniff your farts again when we get home
I have a tummy ache and I just want mine
abies you [__] idiot I told you to
keep that a secret when we're on the
public bus you're making me look bad I
didn't do nothing you make yourself look
bad every day
[Laughter]
Daddy stop laughing you me heads I don't
have any ulterior motive I swear my
conscience is clear as Crystal more like
as clear as your [__] when you're
done pooping on your [__]
[Laughter]
toddler
we're here what do you think honey buns
this is where we're spending our trip
where is all the palm trees and sexy
hola dancing chicks saying
Aloha mama you said we were going on
vacation this is just the motel two
blocks down the road from our house I
demand that you take me back at one
oh you guys I know it's not quite what
you expected certainly not Paris or Rome
but at least it's something right I
worked a whole 8 years for this trip
that cost me
$37 won't you give it to CH no if my
rich boyfriend Bart lebby saw me in a
place like this I might as well kill
myself tell us our room number so we can
leave and hide from the public until the
day after tomorrow when we drive home
here we are room number six give me
that haha check it sibs if you move the
six to the front and flip it upside down
it literally says poo haaha manic you
are so funny you really showed our mom
what what thanks bro yeah that's a good
one haha how in the world did you notice
that shut up [__] you have been ruining
this whole vacation since we got here
you're not allowed to talk for the next
1 minute and 2 seconds or sonic will
beat you the [__]
up
okay come on bro let's find our room and
sit on the bed with our arms crossed to
Show Mommy that we are really
angry thanks a ton mommy you pull this
[__] and you wonder why we get the cops
called on us for domestic
abuse well while we're here we might as
well make the most of it how about
ordering some room service I could go
for a chicken
tnder don't even think about it little
man if you want to act like a couple of
toddlers you're going to eat like babies
do we're having baloney and cheese
sandwiches tonight baloney and cheese
sandwiches from where do you plan to
obtain such crude things
woman
okay Sonia it's been 1 minute and 2
seconds so you can start talking again
yay I'm going to celebrate by calling
Knuckles and making kissy noises in the
phone this Motel doesn't have Wi-Fi oh
sibs check it we found the ice machine
the Sonic Underground does it again how
does it work I think you put the bucket
under where the ice Falls and just press
the button Sonia shut up bro stop
telling our sister to shut up press the
button you I don't want to press it what
if some stranger rubbed his balls on it
manic why are you so straight well why
are you such a [__] queer you [__]
sister I defended
you okay it's okay Sonia I forgive you
because I know that elers came from a
place of Love since gay people have a
high [__] suicide rate oh I don't
care about that I would actually prefer
it if you killed yourself if it will
make you hedgehogs feel better I will
press the button after all what are the
chances that random gay guy rubbed his
balls on it
anyway here's the ice
bucket
and CH next to the toilet where are
going to for the next qu
[Applause]
hours I have emptied my ass into this
toilet and I now need to replenish my
belly with an edible substance manic be
it all and go ask our very own
biological mother for financial support
so we can get Fuego talkis from on the
bending machine in the
[Music]
hall mama can we have some quarters for
the vending machine my purse is on the
bed get it yourself [__] boy yeah [__]
boy I ain't going anywhere near that
thing a comment on you YouTube informed
me that purses are they manic guys can
carry around purses too what about Tinky
Winky from the T bees Emerald brother
have you yet procured the doubloons from
the Hideous landlocked C
Banshee he's just a purple technological
baby that gets stons of [__] not a
set of balls up the ass damnn manic okay
I had no idea you were such a devoted
fan of the teletab
bees Sonia put the C in I can't I'm
holding my pumpkin spice latte make
Sonic do it what where did you get a
pumpkin spice
latte don't worry about
it it didn't work try
[Music]
again try doing it slower bro I'm Sonic
the Hedgehog speed is the only thing I
know
[Music]
oh hell yeah who's ready for some
takies I think the Takis got stuck a
great it's like the Takis want to
participate in making Society worse damn
this Mexican snack be acting like
Mexican people bu in this [__] am I
right Subs okay I don't know why you
felt like being racist out of nowhere
yeah bro that was pretty random where
did that come from shut up bro don't
tell our sister to shut up shut up queer
shut up [__] yeah shut up [__] you
shut up you style your hair like Cloud
Strife from Final Fantasy hoping you can
get a babe like def but you won't cause
your ugly that's enough both of you our
hairstyles are all special and unique
without them we would all look the same
are those my two favorite hedgehogs and
Sonic wow sick are you guys on a
vacation too Knuckles you're here too of
course in fact I was just heading down
to the pool me and my great-grandfather
are having ourselves a little
getaway you mean to say you want to be
here at this crusty ass Hotel there
isn't anywhere else I would want to be I
know it's not much but a air put this
strip all together solely out of the
kindness of his heart and I think that
is really
cool isn't that why you're here didn't
your mom do the same thing for you your
stupid ass probably but we sort of threw
a big fit about it it's not our fault
though because she made it seem like a
bigger trip than it actually was well
that's pretty cold I bet your mom put in
a lot of work too if I were you I would
apologize to her right now come on Subs
it is time for us to do what is
right my life sucks I didn't even want
to come on this stupid vacation in the
first place nlas made Me by force that
[__] stole my wallet and rented a hotel
room without my permission and he
ordered all the room service and he
won't even let me have one bite and now
he's out in the hallway lying to those
hedge or brats making it sound like this
whole thing was my idea I should be sad
but instead I'm so full of
Rage hey Sonic isn't that your handsome
billionaire
boyfriend Hey look if it isn't my [__]
and a couple of his friends how have you
L been haaha quit playing around
Bartleby they're not my friends they're
my siblings you know that right siblings
uh-huh I knew that you have a couple of
those yep I love my lover enough to know
he has siblings uhhuh so how are you
doing Sonic and
and anyway as I was saying before you so
rudely interrupted me Bart leby why are
you in your tidy
whes uhuh I was waiting for you to
notice see I had a meeting I thought it
was going to be a zun call so I put on a
shirt later to find out it was in person
so when I went out the door I forgot to
put on pants can you believe it do you
want me to ask my mom if she can drive
home and get you a pair of pants [__] I
just spoiled my britches with ging hot
[__] it's [__] over now excuse me
well I go in there and do my second duty
of the
[Music]
[Applause]
day because you saw the looks on their
faces no matter what I do I'm always the
bad guy so I'm walking home that way
when one more thing goes wrong they
won't have me to blame well your s
Please Don't Go Mama we don't want you
to go you're not the bad guy we are it's
not your fault that we failed to take
into account all the hard work you do we
were kind of selfish and [__] we didn't
even give the strip a chance so please
don't be sad mama please don't cry
because we are terrible kids yeah [__]
oh Sonia don't say that we're not
terrible at all I should have thought
about what you wanted instead of going
for what's cheap no no mother should
ever put herself before her kids if
anyone should go home it's us because we
are a trio of bad
[Music]
eggs come on Subs it's time to juice and
by juice I mean walk
home Knuckles the Aida what's up oh you
didn't hear well let me cat catch you up
to speed you me Paul your boyfriend Bart
will be mon Clara Dresden the richest
man alive has just finished his business
meeting 45 seconds ago really that's
great to hear oh no it ain't he just
bought this entire Hotel so he called
for everyone inside to be evicted by
3:00 and so we can't tell anybody we all
have to go line up in front of a
government to shoot firing squad
downstairs so they can kill us oh gosh
you can't be serious [__] do I look
[__] they're even handing out free
bottles of water and Rit crackers as an
incentive to not run away well [__] I
paid $37 for this room if I'm going to
die then I at least deserve rein first
who's with me [__] I just rather not
die at
all why bleby why are you so cruel to us
[__] you [__] you man you deserve death
it was certainly a pleasure doing
business with you all my apologies for
smothering the leather seat in poo poo
but that happens oh what's that you're
crying because your family is staying in
this hotel and will now die and it's all
because I showed up threatening their
lives with imminent destruction you mean
like
this look there he is that's the guy
trying to kill us
all what is the meaning of this
we poor people are not going to let you
get away with this montcla you think you
have the power to do whatever you want
because you're part of the 1% yes well
that's all I got Sonic or should I use
your preferred title my [__] it does
not have to be this way come here and
grab my muscular hand lest you wish to
join your family with the firing squad
downstairs bro don't do it yeah he's
just trying to get inside of your head
[Music]
fool you think I didn't realize the pink
and the others were simp our
[Music]
distraction what are you doing just
laying there run for your life little
baby
oh I don't think so big
man [__] what the [__] is wrong with
you why on Earth are you protecting such
a lowquality establishment such as this
because because we rented a room here no
that's too bad because I don't give a
[__] firing squad
fire
there now that the hotel is gone nobody
gets what they want are we all satisfied
now not quite I still spent my entire
bank account on this F A so I'm short
$37 where are my kids supposed to sleep
for the next 2 days how about at our
house we wouldn't mind sharing our own
place with friends I can even cook us
all up some prep Nick it's an aidant
delicacy you know and of course Bartley
can come too Bart
leby I suppose I can stop by tonight for
dinner
anyway yes and before I forget I have a
little gift for
you I noticed you accidentally broke
your old one a minute ago so here's an
even better one it's made from the most
expensive plastic you can buy at Walmart
and to finish it off by stray painted it
with yellow paint it's
lovely
[Music]
okay
foree
[Music]
[Applause]
foree